[
    {
        "id": "UK-10",
        "question": "What did the ancient Greeks use for toilet paper?",
        "answer": "Stones"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-16",
        "question": "Inventor Nicola Tesla never married, but claimed to have fallen in love with ______ instead.",
        "answer": "A pigeon"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-20",
        "question": "What does Adele have a fear of?",
        "answer": "Seagulls"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-23",
        "question": "If someone is playing with a 'quockerwodger', what are they playing with?",
        "answer": "A puppet"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-24",
        "question": "What did Roman Emporer Caecus ban for nearly 200 years?",
        "answer": "The letter Z"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-26",
        "question": "Queen Elizabeth II is fully trained ______.",
        "answer": "Mechanic"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-27",
        "question": "In Arizona, what is illegal to put in your bathtub after 7pm?",
        "answer": "A donkey"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-31",
        "question": "In WWII, what did the Royal Navy call a cat who survived being on three ships that sank?",
        "answer": "Unsinkable Sam"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-43",
        "question": "In the movie Braveheart, what was accidentally filmed in the background during a battle scene?",
        "answer": "A car"
    },
    {
        "id": "UK-48",
        "question": "What item worth 407,000$ was stolen from a Spanish hotel in 2021?",
        "answer": "A bottle of wine"
    }
]